Brother, today mom refused to let me go to the swimming pool
but I
made a swimming pool at home but in the end something
happened which was not even expected.  Mom, if
Katie and I want to go to the swimming pool, let's go.
Yes friend, I haven't gone for a long time.   I will
break your legs if you dare to go anywhere.   I
told you.
Yes mom, these people have started doing a lot of hawala business.  I
will see you later son.
Katie, come with me.
A Few Moments Later.
What will he do now in this heat?  Hey, so what if you ca
n't go to the swimming pool?
Three to one.
Oh wow what af.
Hey, I'm going to take a bath.
Okay [nasal voice] son,
why did I stop you from going to the swimming pool,
you made a swimming pool at home?
Mummy.  [MUSIC]
And then Mommy came along.  But I
thought mom would be angry.  But here
mom herself started enjoying the bowler's top.